

Rekunova Maria

Info

8 February 1997 Kyiv, Ukraine ma.rekunova@gmail.com +38 (063) 726 60 43

About Me

I am a highly organized digital designer & developer. With a passion for animation and strong attention to detail, I'd like to put my skills, experience, and creativity to use to help bring your projects to life. I am engaging, productive, and ready to work on challenging projects to expand my knowledge, improve my English, and reach new achievements together.

Languages

Ukrainian Native

Russian Native

Englsih Upper - intermediate (B2)

German Beginner (A1)

Hobbies

Sport, painting, travelling, cinematography

Education

2014 - 2018 Bachelor Degree Specialist in automation and computer-integrated technologies

Kyiv National University of Technologies and Design

2018 - 2019Master Degree

Computer systems and automation reserch engineer

Kyiv National University of Technologies and Design

Skills

• HTML5, CSS3/SASS

After Effects

Javascript (basic)

• GSAP animation library

• Photoshop, Figma, Illustrator

Sony Vegas

Experience

July 2019 present time

Digital Designer

Inskin Media

- creating mock-ups for a range of devices using providing assets & following brand guidelines;
- developing rich media adverts using HTML, CSS, JS/Query
- usage of GSAP animation library, native CSS3 animation, sprite sheets;
- collaborating with international teams, going through a manager-client process, managing multiple campaigns at any one time

September 2018

Junior Digital Designer

Inskin Media

April 2016 -January 2017 Shop-assistant

Argo

June 2015 -August 2015

Cashier Novus

Certificates

First Certificate in English Kyiv, 2014

FCE confirms an upper-intermediate level of English

Personal Qualities

Responsible, highly organized, detail-oriented, problem solving initiative, communicative, easy-going